Olga Pavlovskaia Procurement Specialist

Yerevan, Armenia · 37 493 544 879 · oa.pavlovskaia26@gmail.com · https://www.linkedin.com/in/olga-pavlovskaia/

SUMMARY

Procurement Specialist with over 6 years of experience in procurement. Implemented Miro's procurement system from scratch, adapting the procurement process to the company's needs and reducing approval times by 27%. Coordinated the procurement process at all stages, processing over 100 requests monthly. Proven experience in selecting optimal suppliers, negotiating and concluding profitable partnerships.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Procurement Specialist

Oct 2022 - Nov 2024

Miro, Yerevan, Armenia

An online collaboration platform for distributed teams used by 30 million people worldwide, including teams from Netflix, Twitter, Airbnb, Cisco, Spotify.

- Implemented a procurement tool in 2 months, improving processes, reducing timelines and increasing overall operational efficiency.
- Developed and optimised workflows in the system to speed up the approval process, reducing approval time by 27%.
- Developed SOP for procurement processes, ensuring uniformity and adherence to best practices across departments.
- Managed vendor data in the procurement system, creating and updating over 70 requisitions monthly.
- Managed onboarding of new employees by training 2 new team members in 3 months.

Procurement Coordinator

Jul 2021 – Oct 2022

- Updated tools list by eliminating analogues and consolidating subscriptions from different teams into one, reducing tools by 48 items and associated costs by \$250K.
- Coordinated all phases of the procurement process, processing over 100 requisitions monthly.
- Ensured compliance with corporate regulations, industry standards, and budgetary constraints while procurement processes.
- Interacted with internal stakeholders (Finance, Operations, and others) and vendors to ensure procurement processes ran smoothly.

Foreign Operations Manager

Sep 2018 - Jun 2021

Reliable Partner Ltd, Russia, Perm

One of the largest companies in Russia for wholesale supply of motorbike equipment of exclusive brands VENTO (VMC) and SADD, on the market for more than 25 years.

- Worked with Chinese partners and licensing authorities of the Russian Federation, obtaining a certificate of conformity for import of motorbike equipment from China.
- Conducted analysis of the transport services market, building profitable logistics schemes for the company.
- Managed the full cycle of purchases from placing an order at the factory to receiving the goods at the warehouse, coordinated the logistics of shipments.
- Worked with customs authorities to comply with regulatory requirements.

EDUCATION

- Perm State University, Master's Degree in Banking and Finance, Russia, 2018.
- Perm State University, Bachelor's Degree in Global Economy, Russia, 2016.

CERTIFICATES

- Successful Negotiations: Essential Strategies and Skills, University of Michigan, 2022.
- Admin training for ZIP (ERP system), 2021.

LANGUAGES

Russian: Native, English: C1, Chinese: B1.

SKILLS

Procurement Process Optimization, Negotiation, SAP Ariba, Contract Management, Oracle Procurement, Supplier Relationship, Cost Reduction, Market Analysis, Spend Analysis, Risk Management, Inventory Management, Coupa Software, Data Analysis, Compliance Monitoring.